Many business owners have clear ideas,
products, market and vision
But the problem is, who will make the
website, who will handle the Instagram, who
will design the label
What about the launch sequence and
consistency?
recently while working with a pet care brand
I saw exactly the same
founder had a vision
we made a website
started Instagram
made a label of 9 products
created an execution structure for the
launch
We designed labels for nine products.
they don't just need advice, they need
someone who can tell them to execute this
and this is my role in Shikha Solutions
They need someone alongside them to help
turn ideas into execution.
I will answer 3 questions
If your business is running but execution
has gaps, comment GAP.